[music]
wake up every day.
>> So, there's a temporary travel ban
leaving the Caribbean towards the United
States where we can't. [music]
>> Good morning, ladies and gentlemen. We
are about to departure to billionaire
weekend in St. Barts. It's the size of a
[__] grain of rice, brother. It's
like you could go from one point of the
island to the other in 10 minutes on a
[__] golf cart. And it's a problem
because this [__] can't land there. It's
just too big. So, we're going to
actually take this to St. Martin. Then
from St. Martin, we have a yacht that's
going to take us to the island. And then
we're going to spend a week on a yacht
for New Year's. It's actually my first
time actually spending New Year's out of
my home without my family. It's pretty
weird, but you know, new experiences. I
want to start off the year different.
2025 for me was uh more of like a
learning year uh than like a achievement
year. Not right. We did a Yeah, I know.
[laughter]
>> I know. You're right. You're right.
You're right. You're right. You're
right. You know what? But we know we
could have had [__] four and I
crashed. I took that kind of, you know,
[__] it up, but then I got it back.
So, I made it back.
It's 7:00 in the morning. Let's Let's
Let's get out of here. So, we're on the
way to St. Bart.
You still got [__]
[music]
in the
standing.
I give you my
>> I just ced it. Thanks, brother, for the
gift. Appreciate it. That [__] looks
hard on me.
>> Tax tax right off
the man. Ready?
>> When I was in Monaco, everyone's like,
"Yo, that's a sick watch." I I had the
purple one at the time and I was like
going for like I would say 285. come
back from Monaco, I land and I swear
like Sean's like, "Yo, I might have
someone for the watch. The market's
going up." And the guy offered us 295,
which is like 10k over market. I'm like,
"Fuck." Like, it's good. Before I sell
the watch, I swear 2 weeks later, I'm
looking to replace it and it cost me
330. Jumped like 30% in a week. I was
like, "What the fuck?" What's this at
right now?
>> Close to 400.
>> 400 next week.
>> You got that right. [laughter]
>> He He gave me even collaterals.
>> Even collateral.
Made a [__]
You watch the car. Look good. Look good.
>> Yeah, you watch the car.
>> All right, boys. We just landed in St.
Martin. Yo, it [__] feels like GTA.
Straight off the jet, pulling up to the
[__] yacht.
>> That's the yacht.
>> Yeah. What's wrong with this,
>> brother? It's it's it's billionaire week
in St. Barts. This you know how hard you
know how expensive it is to even get
this year.
>> This is the best we could do. We worked
hard all this year for this.
>> We haven't [__] all week. [laughter]
>> But no, we're talking [__] We're
pulling up in this boat right here. So,
it's actually crazy. There's over 3,000
yachts in St. Barts. This is billionaire
week in St. Barts and I want to see what
all the hype is about. All the yachts
here are over 150 ft, the big boys. And
we're probably in the smallest boat
here. So, right now it's day one. It's
Monday, December 29th. We're going to
try and make 2 to 300k this week on the
boat and see what St. Bart's all about.
So, let's get on.
Send the wire.
Send it
[music]
from the 12 to 12.
Not the least compelled [music]
by anyone but yourself.
>> I can definitely hear more than all of
you guys for sure.
>> 100%.
>> Let's test it out.
>> No, no. I I could I 100% hit more than
you guys.
>> You say that out there. Just hit 100
pushes.
>> I don't know how you do that. You're the
best.
>> Okay. You want me to hit 100 push-ups
and then and then I go?
>> Yeah. You won't even do 100, bro.
>> I know you.
>> So, I'm going to hit 100. No, but you
you've hit 75. I've been counting.
>> No,
>> 90 to be exact.
>> I did three sets of 30.
>> Yeah, 90.
>> Okay. I'll hit 90. I'll hit 90 and then
we'll go then we'll do the competition.
>> I feel like the like the Wolf of Wall
Street. She said, "You're [__] fun
coupons, bitch."
>> Yeah.
[music]
Yeah.
Too much.
[music]
Too much
too much.
[music]
Too much.
>> Good morning.
>> Good morning indeed.
>> Morning. You know, it was supposed to be
a great morning. I was supposed to wake
up and wake up with beautiful ocean
views, blue skies, blue waters, and get
ready for this 2026 with my new goals
and my new ambitions. But yeah, all
that's going out the window right now. I
decided to come here early in the
morning. Come in here. Don't worry. Have
clothing on. I decided to take my
morning Well, don't worry. Don't worry.
All right. You're safe in here. All
right. Don't worry. You're safe. I
decide to come in here and take my
morning uh number two. And as I sit down
right here, for whatever reason, I
decide to look back.
And then I realize my 2026 goals ain't
[__] [laughter]
That's Jeff Bezos.
>> Isn't that Walmart? That is the founder.
No, I think that's that. Who is that?
That's the niece, right? It's like It's
like the niece of the founder of
Walmart. So there's like Walmart, then
there's like the kids, then there's like
the niece. That's the nieces. That shows
you how much wealth and how far it goes.
You can see your very gear.
>> Yeah, you can see it,
>> brother. What about like that?
>> Yeah, you can even see it clear,
>> brother.
>> It's just like,
I don't know. I think that's probably
like $2 $300 million. So, I woke up like
this. I'm taking my [__] and I look back
and I'm like,
>> whoa. [__] came out even faster.
[laughter]
Like, whoa, whoa.
>> Apart from the boat rocking left and
right. Oh yeah. Yeah, dude. This is why
you need a bigger boat, too, bro. This
[__] doesn't stop moving. It's like it's
big, don't get me wrong, but it's not
big enough. Like, the size of the boat
does matter. It's not the motion in the
ocean.
>> That is the motion in the ocean.
>> No, but this the the motion in the ocean
is affecting this boat because of the
size of the boat. The motion in the
ocean right now is not affecting that
boat because of the size of that boat.
So, the size of the boat doesn't matter.
>> You get what I'm saying?
>> Oh, man. Long story short,
back to the drawing board with my goals.
Nancy Pelosi, Jeff Bezos, whoever the
[__] that is.
Thank you for accelerating my morning
[__] [laughter]
So, we found out that taxis don't exist
out here.
>> Yeah, dude. Everyone's like super
packed. I don't know. Like, it's just
like non-existent having a taxi or a
driver. Is this our guy?
>> No. Doesn't have 300
dark blue. That's a gray.
>> Oh, these guys are having a fun time.
[music]
>> Put a bill in there. Same text.
That's what a billionire insane part
looks like.
I'm level four. All right. So, I'm in
the [__] camera. We're going to go to
NY's yacht. I'm see put it at 100. So,
right now it's at 50.
Put it on. I'll go secure some
generations. We're going to go dig.
We're going to go get
We're going to try and get into
Nancy's boat.
Lock in our generational wall. Oh, wait.
There's a boat coming. Oh [__]
Wait. Come back this way. We going to
get run over. Oh, we almost got run
over.
All right, let's go. All
right, Nancy is going to make it right
now.
All right, Nancy and the kids [music]
will be there soon. You know, people
probably expect Oh,
people probably expect to get you a
drink, party all the time. Actually,
don't. We've been here for like 3 days.
Every day we just sitting on the boat.
We're talking more business than ever
because just five entrepreneurs,
business savvy guys talking about 2026
and how we're going to [__] rip it
and potentially
get one of these right there. So
today
cardio
[music]
It's been a nice [singing] life. Money
and a bright light. [music]
Ain't as bad as people describe.
I've been [music] a nice guy. People
I've done right by. [singing] Flip.
Don't mean. But girl, it's all right.
It's [music] all right. It's all right.
It's all right. It's all right. Not
surprised by nothing. I just take it and
[music] try.
On the bright [singing] side, everyone
on [music] my side, they still got their
love and they pride. I get the more I
want [singing and music]
I for your love
the more I [music]
stole that [__]
[music]
[music] tenders the seat belts. are
currently under
>> maintenance.
>> Maintenance.
>> Other timber doesn't work.
>> Jet ski.
>> Jet ski doesn't work.
>> Jet ski is broken. We want to go to
land, but there's no way to get a land
this resort island. So, we're going to
swim there. Rich's a You're a
professional swimmer, right?
>> I take that as a yes. So am I. You're
not.
>> All right. So, we're on the way. Yo,
Ritz, you actually know how to swim,
right?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do.
>> Yeah,
>> I've done like island to island swim
before.
>> That's straight cap. For sure.
>> [__] lying.
>> Figure out right now.
>> I I did it like this. Look,
the whole the whole way through.
I did not swim to another [__]
island.
>> We're going against the the current
right now.
We're already [__] tired,
>> bro. We've done nothing,
>> bro. I feel really have swam nothing. We
haven't moved.
All right, time to lock in. A lot of
people are going to think that we're
capping. A lot of people are going to
think that we're capping. We're not.
Boat's still there. We're a little bit
closer to the island. I'm doing this for
my [__] ancestors.
I immigrated from Cuba. Can't let them
down.
>> No. We're almost there.
I think I just saw a fish under me.
I'm just tired. I'm heavy as [__] right
now. 190 lbs of pure Cuban muscle.
I'm not going to lie. I've done a lot of
crazy workouts, but this is just
[__] We're almost there.
I've been swimming for like 20 minutes.
I'm the last guy. My guns are almost I'm
the last guy, but my guys
look at this guy.
>> Well, we're going back now, right?
>> No, [laughter]
>> brother. I'm not leaving this island.
>> So, are you going to swim back out or
>> Probably not. [laughter]
>> Probably not.
>> Uh,
>> that's a long swim, right? Or no?
>> Well, to be honest with you, a few
months ago, there was a guy they swim
from Anguela straight to St. in 5 hours.
>> 5 hours.
>> You see, he said it's cap. [laughter]
>> I said it's cap if you did it like but I
did a leg. I swear.
>> I mean that guy's a that guy's a psycho.
>> I can do it 100% if you give me fins.
Fins and a snorkel and a mask.
>> Yeah, you
>> free free swim. Free swim.
>> Nothing.
>> No fin.
>> Dude's a [__] fish,
>> dude. What the [__] They have solar
powered fans.
[laughter]
>> Yeah, I didn't even notice that.
>> Solar powered fans. Yeah, that's sick.
>> Who engineered that, dude? Who thought
of that, bro? This
>> It's a million dollar idea. A billion
dollar idea,
>> bro. That guy probably sold and is
insane Barts on the boat right now.
>> Can I take a picture, man?
>> Let me see, bro.
I I I want you in the picture, man. I
want you in the picture. There you go.
>> What What you guys are staying in St.
BS? You know, you must be
>> uh
>> some famous. He's famous.
>> No, no, no.
>> This one here with I'm just recording
cuz I'm very forgetful. I'm forget I'm
[laughter] forget this conversation in
like 15 minutes.
>> I'm a [clears throat] forgetful kind of
guy, you know. [laughter]
>> Record everything. Go back. You know, so
like he remembers all of it.
>> But you you're unforgettable, my
brother.
>> Yeah, man. Like Jamaica, man.
>> You know what set and forget mean?
>> Set unforgettable.
>> Well, what do you think it means?
>> You just you set and you forget.
>> Yeah. Like right now you're going to go
give that man that drink. That man with
that drink is set and forgetting.
>> Well, it can be it sound a bit like
something good.
>> It's amazing.
>> It also, you know, I don't want to
think. [laughter]
>> No, it's there's no wrong. You You just
You just tell us what you think it is.
>> Yeah.
>> You You can walk there and think about
it. Let us know when you
>> telling me a bunch of stuff.
>> What did he say?
>> I don't know.
>> [screaming]
[screaming]
>> All right. So, I'm taking over now.
>> We just finished volleyball. Now, we're
racing.
And after going back to the yacht. So,
the founder of Fashion Nova is that mega
yacht right there. We were eating in the
exact same restaurant as him, which is
this one right here. And one of the
girls went up to him. We're like, "Hey,
this might be super random, but are you
whatever his name is, the founder of
Fashion Nova?" And he's like, "Yeah,
that's who I am. I came here for New
Year's and now there was too much noise
in St. Barts, so now I'm here." So
that's his mega yacht right there. Oh,
wait. They're racing.
>> Oh, they're all [__] so slow.
>> Yeah. Long story short, is why you got
to be in dope places,
>> right?
>> Indeed. and without a phone especially.
>> Oh yeah. So you lost your phone.
>> So we don't know how much of the YouTube
video is going to come out.
>> Yeah. If this video seems a little bit
empty is because half of the content was
recorded on the phone because we were
trying to get into these high-end places
but they didn't allow cameras. So we
couldn't record on the camera. We
couldn't bring the cameras. We record on
the phone. Seas potentially lost his
phone in the bottom of the ocean.
>> My dolphin dive into the ocean holding
Alex's phone. Not my phone. in my pocket
when I come up. Pock is where I'm home.
>> Yeah, I if that's the case, bro, I could
100% get your phone. I can see it right
now when we go back. But yeah, this is
why you got to be around other
successful people. You know what's
crazy? Sal has mentioned this to me 6
years ago. I used to go into Lamborghini
stores, Bugatti stores, and walk in and
envision
>> like high-end restaurants, be outside of
these cool places, and just like
envision myself being in these places
and normalizing it. Now it's very much
the normal. And now I'm here around
billionaires. The CEO of Fashion Nova,
Jeff Bezos, Nancy Watson, when she got
me a gift, which is [__] I imagine
getting a gift from a billionaire, bro.
[laughter]
>> Yo, a billionaire. [music]
Like, what better way to start off the
year by having a billionaire recognize
you and give you a gift. I just think
it's cool.
>> Still racing.
>> Jacob, you're a [__] cheater, bro.
>> You guys jumped on me.
>> The moral of the story, Horal story.
This is why we like surrounding
ourselves now in this type of [__]
because soon this will be the normal.
>> All right. So today's mission, Operation
Save Sebastian's phone. So you care to
explain what happened yesterday?
>> So yesterday when I dolphin dove into
the water, we lost my phone. And my
phone is the most important phone in
this whole trip.
>> Yeah. What's on your phone, sir?
>> All the content.
>> Yeah. So, if you guys in this vlog feel
like it's a bit empty or there's
something missing, it's because uh
this phone is at the bottom of the
ocean. So, now it's going to be
operation [music]
find.
I think I think I got it, bro. I'm not
going to lie.
>> Trust me, I believe in you.
>> Did you have a iPhone case on it or no?
>> Yeah.
>> What color is it? Black.
>> Black.
>> Straight black.
>> Yeah.
>> You'll find it.
>> What's the phone number?
>> Yeah.
I'm in the mason room at the BB Blows.
The boat was rocking too much on some
Aaliyah [__]
for real.
We going from the VA to sink on sink,
[music] then back to the VA. If you
know, you know, baby. I don't I don't
know what to tell you.
>> Yeah.
[music]
Hey,
am I red? Hey, you look like a lobster.
No,
>> I don't look like Mike Thirstston.
with like his tan and [__] We're
pulling up right now to St. Martin. The
real real big boy yachts can't even come
in here right now. They're actually like
way over there.
Did Did they see the part already of
where I got the gift from the
billionaire?
>> No. I don't think we've given them that
much context yet.
>> We definitely did. Hit us up and forget.
[laughter]
>> Well, because we don't know how much
content was on your phone, bro. So,
okay. So, let me give you guys a little
bit of context. So, I I haven't been on
TikTok my whole entire life. I opened up
a Tik Tok like 3 months ago cuz
apparently everybody's on TikTok except
me. I I've never even scrolled through
the platform. So I said, "Fuck it. I'm
going to open one up and just post
random [__] that I do." And I had the
bright idea to record Sebas and I
attempting to sneak into a mega yacht.
>> We're on the way to Ni's boat.
>> Now, us attempting to sneak into this
mega yacht is just us just doing being
fun. You know, we generally like doing
cool things, being authentic, and just
being ourselves and putting it out
there. not even thinking of how people
are going to react to it because we're
just having fun and we know we're not
going to harm anybody. Tik Tok goes
viral and Tik Tok goes so viral that the
yacht that we were trying to sneak onto
is Nancy Walton's yacht. Also, a family
member of the founders of Walmart, $400
million yacht. And guess who happens to
see the Tik Tok? Nancy Walton. Nancy
Walton sees the [__] Tik Tok. And
guess what I get? I get a DM by one of
her best friends, one of her family
members, a cousin, someone, and they
didn't want to describe to me who it
was, and it said this. Nancy Walton
thought that it was hilarious that I was
trying to sneak onto her [__] yacht.
Now, if I would have told anybody about
this idea, they would have said, "Hey,
that's a cringe idea. That's a bad idea.
Don't do it. We don't operate like that.
We do whatever the [__] we want." Long
story short, fast forward 24 hours.
Well, to give you guys more context, the
NY's yacht leaves in the afternoon. We
had a billionaire goodbye wave. They
leave. very sad afternoon because you
know I love waking up every single
morning to seeing her there. No big
deal. The next day we go to a different
island which is Angia Angia. Anguila
>> Anguila
>> who cared
whatever and we wake up for breakfast.
In the middle of us having breakfast
going into the water we see chaos's
tender circling the island and like
identifying us and they didn't tell me
that they were going to pull up to where
we were going to be. They found our
location. I don't know how the [__] and
they gifted me a bottle. I got a gift by
a billionaire on the second day of the
year.
>> Who gifted you something on the second
day of the year? Do I have a strict mama
now? Yes, I maybe do. Do I no longer
have to trade? Maybe I maybe no longer
have to trade. Maybe this is all I had
to do to make it out the hood and
finally be rich. Find a billionaire
wife. You won't do it. So, I don't know.
I thought that was pretty cool that I
got recognized by a billionaire. to give
us a gift. And uh just the fact that
that even happened, you know, like you
can't even
can't even wake up and think that
something like that's going to happen.
It's the most random thing ever. All
because Sam and I thought it was a good
idea to be our subs and put it out there
on the internet. So right now we're in
St. Martin as we speak. We're supposed
to leave tonight back to Miami. We've
been here for a week already, bro. It's
the longest vacation we've ever had.
Actually, it's an actual vacation. I'm
not going to lie. I haven't opened my
laptop once. So, as as we're speaking
right now, it is January
the 3rd.
And uh guess what happened January the
3rd? If you're watching this in the
future, you might not remember, but
Trump just captured that [__]
Maduro. That means now Maduro is a
Maduro. If you don't know what a Maduro
is, this is what it looks like. It means
he's cucked. But he's cucked. But we're
also cooked because now that now that
Madura is captured, Trump doesn't want
to have anybody travel from the
Caribbean, which is where we are right
now, towards the US. So, there's a
temporary travel ban, quote unquote,
no-fly zone, leaving the Caribbean
towards the United States or
intertwining anywhere in here. Trump put
a no-fly zone in this part of the world
that's not even the US. Great captur.
But now we're [__] Maduros right now
because we're stuck here for 2 days.
Yeah, I know. It look like a tomato, but
we have a travel ban right now where we
can't leave until further notice. So,
yeah, we're going to be here probably
for another 2 3 days until the travel
ban is removed. The jet was on the way
to pick us up and they cancelled it,
bro. The [__] do we even have in Miami
anyways? Oh, you want what we do have in
Miami? Matt Armstrong. Matt Armstrong
pulled up today. He he lands and he's
like, "Hey, mate, I'm here. Where you
at?" Like, "Brother, I'm still in the
Caribbean." He's like, "Oh, okay. Okay,
cool. So, you come tonight, right?" And
I'm like, "Yeah, I was scheduled to come
tonight, but Trump caught our boy. Now
we're cooked." So, he's just there
waiting for us to pull up so we can
start fixing the Bugatti. If you guys
don't know, I crashed a Bugatti a couple
of months ago, bought it back, and we're
fixing it. And my Armstrong flew in
specifically this week to fix it, and
we're not there. So, that's another
problem we have.
>> At least he gets to enjoy Miami before
he goes into free labor.
>> We're going to have free labor for my
Armstrong. Who else can say they did
that?
>> [music]
>> Yo,
>> isn't there like a movie or something
like this? Paradise turned into
paranormal or some [__] I I should ask
Chad GPT. There for sure is a movie
where paradise or something ultra
luxurious turns into like a [__]
nightmare. Not saying that that's what's
happening here, but it kind of feels
like it. We went to the airport because
we were supposed to leave. Our jet was
15 minutes away from landing. We were
tracking the town number and we saw that
it was literally circling St. Martin
waiting for authorization to land. So,
we're on the way to the airport ready to
get on the plane and then guess what?
They cancel the landing authorization
from our jet because the airspace is too
congested. So, they reroute our jet to
Puerto Rico. jet gets to Puerto Rico and
there's 35 jets on the runway looking
for parking for others to take off.
There's like at least like 80 people
with jets trying to get the [__] up out
of here just today alone and all these
couple of other days. I'm sure it's been
more. So, our jet got rerouted to Puerto
Rico and guess what happened? We don't
have authorization to leave from Puerto
Rico because the airspace is so
congested and this airspace is now
closed because of how congested it is.
So right now they're just spitting jets
out of here. But there's a jet leaving
every 3 minutes out of here going
somewhere. It's such a small island that
once that clears up then they're going
to open up to new jets to come in and
then we can get picked up. Problem is
that we're number 52 in that line. Our
jet is literally 52 in that [__]
line. So as of right now 400 p.m.
January 5th. So we were supposed to
leave the second. Three extra [__]
days here, dude. And like I we're we're
great people. I'm having a great time.
Look look at this guy. Look at this guy.
That that [__] just landed on a mega
yacht. Like I left the mega yacht from
here. I think it took that person from a
mega yacht to the airport. Well, we had
to drive there. We're not there yet. But
I mean, I don't mind it because in
moments like these, you know, I I I
really get to realize what I want to do
this year, my journey, and how the [__]
I got here. And what I'm doing right
now, visualizing myself normalizing
these mega yachts right here and the
successful people that I've met, I've
actually been able to have a one-on-one
conversation with every single one of
these guys because we're all on the same
we're all on the same boat,
>> same page.
>> We all have the same problem.
>> Yeah, we're all living on the same
problem. Like, like there's no amount of
money that can fix this type of problem
unless you're like Jeff Bezos and you're
like, "Yo, get me the [__] up." Like
that that dude is out of here, right?
Like that dude has no problem. So, for
now, not complaining. I'm not I don't
want I'm not eager to go home. I don't
have to go home. Thankfully, you know,
everything is taken care of. My dogs, my
chickens, my horses, my cat, they're all
being fed. I'm just gonna enjoy this
right here. Meanwhile, we're here
because in due time, we will be back
home eventually. And when we are back
home, then we go from that point. So, I
mean, easy for you to say, I've been on
a force month for 5 days already.
[laughter]
>> All right, boys. We [__] made it.
I've never been so happy to see a jet in
my [__] life. Let's head back to
Miami. We got Matt Armstrong waiting for
us to rebuild the Bugatti. Let's go,
baby.
Diplomatic [music and singing] immunity.
[__] them. All that peace in that unity.
All that
[music]
cuz [__] started talking to me like
I'm slowing down. Opinions [music] over
statistics of course. Gassed off
journalistic. Come at me and all you
[music] get is the ballistic report.
Booked a private room at Wallally's way
to twist in the court. I got multiolor
[singing] rings like the Olympics
[music] of course at award shows cutting
through the tension of course. Girls
hugging me [music] and asking me what
scent that is. Boy, I be walking around
the six like I invented it boy.